https://www.specorp.com/privacy-policy

Reporting Software Industry Solutions
Spectrum’s Display and Reporting Software Solutions collect and create unique business analytics to give you a complete view of your Call Center.
Whether you need to communicate critical information that affects daily job performance, give flexibility and mobility to management or elevate data from just “facts and figures” into useful information, Spectrum has a solution tailored to your specific needs.
Products
Products
Analytics
Dashboards (XorceView)
Desktops (XorceView)
Email & Mobile Phone Reporting
LCD Screens (VectraView)
Call Center Wallboards
NeXorce
Prelude Express
Prelude Express Lite
Tablets
Web Reports
Call Center Unified Reporting Contact center digital signage and Dashboards
Spectrum call center unified reporting software and contact center display products combine data from the ACD, CRM, WFM, in-house databases and more to provide agents and managers KPI’s that improve performance.
Reviewing critical data items, acting on variances from goals and surveying the agent threshold analytics are all standard practices in contact centers utilizing the Spectrum unified reporting software.
Spectrum publishes real time and historical data to LCD Screens, Desktops, Tablet PC’s, Dashboards, LED Wallboards, Web Based reports, Email and Smart Phones.
Partners
Partners
Avaya Contact Center Reporting Tools
Avaya Aura Contact Center (AACC)
Avaya Aura
Avaya CMS
Avaya IQ
Avaya Operational Analyst (OA)
Desktop Comparison
Multichannel Reporting
Cisco Call Center Software
Enterprise
Express
Genesys
Others
Support
Support
End of Life / End of Support
Maintenance Renewals
Support Web Portal
For Spectrum customers who use our products, we offer http://support.specorp.com to submit a ticket for any of the following:
NeXorce Software
VectraView Software
Ultra-Link Software
V-Display Software
On the support site you will find:
Troubleshooter to find an answer to a problem;
Download manuals, updates and training documents;
Access our knowledge base for frequently asked questions;
Submit a trouble ticket and learn the status of an existing ticket.
Company
Company
Blog
News & Events
Incorporated in 1971, Houston, Texas based Spectrum has consistently been an innovative leader offering a “total solution” that maximizes performance and increases efficiency in companies worldwide, including many Fortune 500 companies.
Spectrum Corporation is a leader in Unified Contact Center Reporting (UCCR). UCCR is a process of extracting real time and historical data from contact center applications, transforming that raw data into information and publishing that information in useable reports for all levels of the contact center. The reports are seen on dashboards, LCD screens, desktops, wallboards, web based reports, email and smartphones.
Spectrum’s strength in the UCCR process lies in the ability to extract and collect the raw data using one of six different methods. This unique strength is what puts Spectrum ahead of others in the contact center reporting arena.
Contact Us / RFQ
Privacy Policy
Home Privacy Policy
Introduction
This Privacy Policy discloses the policies of www.specorp.com (the “Website”) and its operatorSpectrum Corporation (collectively “we” or “us”) regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information you submit to us through the Website.
User Consent
By accessing or otherwise using the Website, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, which is incorporated into and forms a part of the Website’s terms of service.  You expressly consent to the processing and use of your information as described herein.
Types of Information Collected
We collect certain “Personal Information” about you which may include, but is not limited to, information that is personally identifiable such as your name, e-mail address and other associated non-public information.
Collection of Personal Information
We collect Personal Information you voluntarily submit to us through the Website.   It is optional for you to utilize this Website.  If you elect to utilize certain aspects of this Website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information about yourself, such as your first and last name, company name and email address.
Collection of Anonymous Information
We use technology to passively collect and store certain anonymous information that is not tied to a specific identified user which may include, but is not limited to your ip address and browser type.   We, or our authorized  third-party representatives may use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit, the site you immediately came from and the site you immediately go to after accessing the Website.  It will also collect data about the terms you searched, viewed or clicked.  Should you be directed to any other site from the Website, we are not responsible for the acts of other sites and this Privacy Policy does not apply to that site.
or call us today at +1 713 944 6200 , +44 (0) 746 924 5920
Contact Center Reporting Solutions
Photo Gallery
Industries
Products
Partners
Company
Contact Us
All Rights Reserved. Website Design & Development by Nibiru Solutions
Dashboards (XorceView)
Desktops (XorceView)
Email & Mobile Phone Reporting
LCD Screens (VectraView)
Avaya Aura Contact Center (AACC)
Avaya Aura
Avaya CMS
Avaya IQ
Avaya Operational Analyst (OA)
